<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--  Catroid: An on-device graphical programming language for Android devices
      Copyright (C) 2010-2011 The Catroid Team
      (<http://code.google.com/p/catroid/wiki/Credits>)
 
      This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
      it under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License as
      published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the
      License, or (at your option) any later version.
  
      This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
      but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
      MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
      GNU Affero General Public License for more details.
  
      You should have received a copy of the GNU Affero General Public License
      along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<strings>
	<string name="title">Copyright Policy</string>
	<string name="email_link">email</string>
	<string name="directive_link">Directive 2001/29/EC</string>
	<string name="chilling_link">chillingeffects.org</string>
	<string name="copyright_policy_part1">
		The Catroid development team respects the intellectual property of others, as well as our users.
        If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please send us an {*emailLink*}.
    </string>
    <string name="copyright_policy_part2">
		We will promptly process and investigate notices of alleged infringement and will take appropriate actions under the {*directiveLink*} and
		other applicable intellectual property laws. Upon receipt, the Catroid development team may act expeditiously to remove or disable
		access to any material claimed to be infringing. Repeat infringers of third-party copyrights are subject to termination in appropriate circumstances.
    </string>
    <string name="copyright_policy_part3">
		In assessing whether or not a Catroid user has violated your copyrights, please keep in mind that Catroid is an educational
		and not-for-profit initiative, seeking to aid children's learning by providing the tools for them to learn and express themselves using digital technology.
    </string>
    <string name="copyright_policy_part4">
		We hope you also see Catroid not only as a good way of popularizing your creations/website but also as an opportunity
		to do something good for children's education.
    </string>
    <string name="copyright_policy_part5">
		If you choose to make a copyright infringement complaint, please note that we may post your notification,
		with personally identifiable information redacted, to a clearinghouse such as {*chillingEffectsLink*}. Please also note that you may be liable
		for damages (including costs and attorneys' fees) if you materially misrepresent that an activity is infringing your copyright.
    </string>
</strings>
